Even though I want to disagree with you, I get where you're coming from.
When I see black people talking about racism, all that stuff,
I'll be like, what is wrong with these people?
You guys have food, you have EBT, all these things.
And you're here shouting about somebody who's racist too.
Just leave that person and move on.
I feel that way.
Like, why are they always, like, complaining?
But when Black Lives Matter started happening, like, I sat down.
I said, I need to actually know why these people are pained.
And if we look at the history, what they've done to them,
like, if you actually sit down, watch some documentaries,
how they were maltreated, how the...
I don't think if I'm actually born here, I will forgive those people.
I don't care.
It's easier for us Africans that were raised in Africa to feel like they're complaining
because we were raised through struggle.
Like, I barely even have water.
And you, you have water, you're complaining.
But then, it's not about the basic necessity or about how we are raised.
We are raised, like, I don't want to say way better.
We might not have resources, but there are some ways, like,
our own people will not look down on us or put us behind.
So, it's in their...
They're not sure that way.
Like, they just can't overlook it.
And if you sit down and watch everything that the forefathers have been through for you,
I changed my mind.
No, they need to be angry.
However, they should still move forward.
Thank you.